You're a manager, so why are you acting?
I thought she was just trying to leave a good impression.
I'm still collecting keychains of the key.
Why collect that trash?
The whole world's using electronic locks these days.
At least, that was before I noticed her uneasy smile.
By the way, I don't do funny content.
I didn't say a word about that.
At least, it was before I grew curious about Hana Hirose.
Why are you clinging to Eun Ho...
Stop messing with me!
Suzu.
I'm sorry.
Before I wanted to do things I never thought of.
What do you mean?
Sometimes, you have an uneasy smile, like right now.
I didn't think it seemed so unsettling.
But isn't smiling all the time better?
A friend I really like always smiles brightly.
That's just an act, but must you force a smile because of them?
It's more comfortable to see you behave naturally.
Maybe it's a culture difference.
Hey, where are the chopsticks?
Don't you have any?
Why would I have chopsticks? You should've brought them over.
You brought so much stuff, but you don't have chopsticks?
Don't you use chopsticks to cook the noodles?
Why didn't you bring them over?
But how were you planning to eat the chicken wings?
With my hands.
I've never eaten them with my hands.
What are you doing?
Someone forgot to take chopsticks and needs to go get them.
Hang on. I have them in my manager bag.
Where is it...
Here you go.
And yours.
You call that your manager bag?
I thought it was a designer bag.
I carry most essentials around.
So adorable.
The bag. It's cute.
He's sharp.
Maybe it's the perceptiveness of an actor.
Delicious. Would've been a real hassle
if we didn't have chopsticks.
Mom?
Yeah.
I'm doing well.
Okay.
Mom.
How was today?
90 percent of the moon's surface is visible.
But no one has ever seen the hidden side to it.
[Episode 4: Falling Flowers]
Ji Ah!
My lucky charm that gives me courage.
Please make things go well today.
Don't you get tired of doing that?
Ji Ah!
It's a great morning again, isn't it?
[Energy Drink]
It's a crap morning.
Why's that?
Because someone just won't leave me alone.
I'm not trying to bother you.
I'm just saying hi because we're friends.
Ji Ah, take the drinks.
You look tired, so she brought it for you.
I don't need it, so don't bother.
When I tell you to stop, don't do it.
You're really self-centered, you know?
If you want to do something, try listening to what I say.
Ji Ah.
Hey! Shin Ji Ah!
This is really pissing me off.
[Week 3 - First: Hana, Second: Ji Ah]
Hana-chan, come up here.
We should wait until the final week,
but she's been top for three weeks straight.
The gap's really wide, and I've analyzed the success factors.
Firstly, she has positively portrayed Eun Ho and Si Woo.
She has also gathered a global fanbase.
Thank you.
Eun Ho, Si Woo, I bet you're receiving tons of DMs.
I don't check.
Me, neither.
Don't you check?
I check everything.
Alright, let's hear her thoughts and end the class.
There's still time left before this workshop ends,
so let's work hard together!
All the best!
Clap!
Alright, get a good lunch!
- Yes, ma'am!
- Got it.
Yikes.
Are those two still keeping a distance from each other?
It's a real cold war now.
You have my respect.
I'll never survive dating Shin Ji Ah.
Never.
Good lord.
Don't say her name! It stresses me out!
She's charming in ways you'll never know.
I never want to find out! Never!
Hana-chan.
Film a video of us playing basketball.
Why do you need that?
Let's go.
It's awkward with just the manager.
I guess I'll go have fun.
Shoot!
Nice shot!
Take it slow first.
Shoot!
Great job!
Hang on!
Hey!
Si Woo!
Pass!
Are you okay?
Yeah.
That scheming bitch!
Our Eun Ho can't marry into a gangster's family.
No...
Stand over there. You're in the way.
I'll return to the classroom.
Pass.
Score!
Si Woo!
Cheon Si Woo, is this your one-man show?
Hey.
Our Eun Ho should know
how scary that gangster daughter is.
She is scary.
Is she really a gangster's daughter?
Hey, aren't you a pro at digging up people's dirt?
Information gathering.
That's key when being a fangirl.
What's her last name...
I think I saw it on our teacher's table.
"Hello! I'm Hana... Hirose!"
That's it.
Thanks.
Where is she going?
It's that day, right?
Ugh, she...
She said she wanted to meet you, so I brought her along.
Hana-chan is fond of you.
Ji Ah!
Friends link arms in Korea too, right?
Yeah. Let's go.
Let's go.
Ji Ah!
Did I scare you?
[Heat Pack]
Why must the last one be at our house?
It's for a "Get Ready With Me" video
30 minutes before leaving home.
You should've said so.
I'll head back first. You two can buy food back.
Why? Are you hungry?
Yeah, I'm hungry.
Take your time.
What should we buy?
Don't...
take too long.
Si Woo, I can't resist this anymore!
We ate a lot.
Yeah, but aren't we taking too long?
It's okay. He told us to take our time.
And we left some for him.
Near my school in Japan, there's a delicious takoyaki shop.
My friend loves the food there.
She visits it once every week.
She said eating the food there makes her heart so full.
Cute, right?
Or maybe only I think so.
The fragrance of takoyaki reminded me of that.
The memories came flooding back.
Maybe I'm feeling homesick.
You're cute, too.
You're speaking in Japanese?
Maybe your friend's heart feels full
because she's eating with you.
Hana-chan!
Si Woo, you're like a vending machine.
You always offer the words I need to hear.
Even when I haven't even pressed a single button.
Here you go!
Si Woo...
This looks good on you.
This one and... this.
Okay! I'll start filming.
And... start.
First outfit.
How is this?
Here's the second one.
What do you think?
I like this one best.
A kind friend, Si Woo.
I'm wearing this.
I'll change into it.
Done, right?
Casually dressed and aloof Eun Ho.
I'm happy with this.
Let's go.
Nice, done.
Alright...
Do you know Suzu Sakamoto?
Hana-chan, do you want instant noodles?
Sure.
What's wrong? Did something happen?
No, it's nothing.
[Management, Class 3-A]
Our homeroom teacher wants to see you
in the consultation room.
But the bell will ring soon.
Do you know Suzu Sakamoto?
You're here?
Hey, this is all your fault, alright?
What are you talking about?
I hate her to the bone
because of you.
- Hana-chan?
- Yeah.
But she is really trash.
Isn't that why you tossed her away?
Cut the crap and get to the point.
She fled after an attempted murder in Japan.
It's right there when you look up the local papers.
What?
I just uploaded the article with your phone.
How did you...
The password is hella easy, Kim Ba Reun's birthday.
It's right there in the chatroom.
They think you sent it, so go back later.
They need time to read, especially our dear Eun Ho.
Why did you use...
[Violence and Bullying in School Club]
It's my group's account.
I don't want Eun Ho to hate me,
and you want to get rid of her.
It's the perfect trash can.
Just leave it there and climb back to first place.
Anyway, she won't last long.
It's quite a serious case.
Eun Ho's picture!
- Holy cow! Did you see?
- Hurry! Take a look!
Is this real?
Did you see it?
I saw it!
What did I tell you?
Did you read it?
[Violence and Bullying in School Club]
Did you hear about Suzu Sakamoto?
- Is it real?
- Did you read about Suzu Sakamoto?
No! Hana-poof!
Jeez...
Leave it to Ba Reun. Let's get going first.
You search there. I'll take this side.
Hana!
Hana-chan!
Hana-chan.
[Epilogue]
Hana-chan, where are you?
You're already so close.
Don't forget about me, alright?
No, Suzu.
Don't do it.